LADA EGOROVA

@ ladaegorova2899@gmail.com

♠ ladaegorova18

in lada-egorova

SUMMARY

Game Developer with over four years of experience in game programming, Unity development, and backend integration. My expertise lies in building and optimizing interactive gameplay systems to enhance the user experience and reduce crashes. I have a strong background in C#, game architecture, and cross-functional team collaboration. Currently, I am pursuing a Master's in Embedded Systems Security to further develop my technical expertise.

EDUCATION

International Master in Embedded Systems Security

Grenoble INP — Esisar, UGA

☐ Sept 2024 – Ongoing

Valence

Relevant courses:

- Advanced Processor Architecture and SoC Design
- Embedded Systems Security
- Verification and Test of Safe and Secure Embedded Systems
- Dependability and Security of Computing Systems
- Innovation project in a French team "PlaceR", the main goal of which is to improve the computer vision algorithm and to run it on existing robot

B.Sc. in Software and Administration of Information Systems Saint-Petersburg State University

🛱 Sept 2018 - June 2022

Saint-Petersburg

Relevant courses:

- Computer Science
- Models and Architectures of Programs and Knowledge
- Software Technology
- Computer Data Processing Algorithms
- Software Design

STUDENT PROJECTS

Three-dimensional modeling visualization for TRIK Studio CyberTech

Öct 2021 - Jun 2022

TRIK Studio is an integrated development environment designed using QtCreator for children to learn robot programming that features a simulation run that utilizes a 2D virtual robot model. The purpose of the work was to improve the quality of visualization and make it three-dimensional. The problem was solved on Unity engine.

Link to the report

Elevator

NoPayStudio

📋 Jan 2019 - Jun 2019

A hypercasual mobile game made on Unity - the second project in NoPayStudio. The goal is to deliver all elevator passengers to their floors.

Link to the report

Checkout

NoPayStudio

☐ Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

Developing a mobile game in just two weeks at a summer IT school turned out to be a significant project on Unity. The player's task is to scan a product by rotating it with their fingers so that the scan code appears in the center of the screen.

SOFT SKILLS

Hard-working Eye for detail Always on time

Sense of humour Responsibility Mobility

HARD SKILLS

C# Embedded Systems C++ VHDL
Python Unity SQL

LANGUAGES

EXPERIENCE

Gameplay Programmer

Saber Interactive

☐ Sep 2021 - Aug 2024 Saint-Petersburg

- Added BI analytics system to the project from zero to track player behavior and improve the quality of gameplay
- Provided back-end support and integration with the game's front-end
- Participated in developing and implementing the game's logic
- Searched and repaired more than 200 game crashes
- Used to help other departments when they had a high workload

Team Lead of Al Training Department Toloka

- Assisted to more than 100 experts during 3 different projects: answers to questions, solving problems with tasks, consultations
- Encouraged the teaching of artificial intelligence by developing valuable content in mathematics and computer science
- Reviewed over 500 texts using artificial intelligence to enhance the quality of the content

Game Developer

NoPayStudio

📋 Jul 2019 - Mar 2020

Moscow

- Developed and tested 2 mobile games projects, including a product scanning game and an elevator passenger delivery game
- Implemented features and integrated UI elements to enhance user experience
- Achieved successful project completion and launch, showcasing strong coding and debugging skills